It's time to step up
Spider-Man: Far From Home is a action, adventure,
science fiction film directed by Jon Watts.
Peter Parker and his friends go on a summer trip to Europe.
However, they will hardly be able to rest - Peter will have to agree to help Nick Fury uncover the
mystery of creatures that cause natural disasters and destruction throughout the continent.
Peter Parker / Spider-Man, played by Tom Holland.
Quentin Beck / Mysterio, played by Jake Gyllenhaal.
Nick Fury, played by Samuel L. Jackson.
May Parker, played by Marisa Tomei.
Happy Hogan, played by Jon Favreau.
MJ, played by Zendaya.
Spider-Man: Far From Home is a 2019 American superhero film based on the Marvel Comics character Spider-Man,
co-produced by Columbia Pictures and Marvel Studios, and distributed by Sony Pictures Releasing.
It is the sequel to Spider-Man: Homecoming (2017) and the 23rd
film in the Marvel Cinematic Universe (MCU).
The film was directed by Jon Watts, written by Chris McKenna and Erik Sommers, and
stars Tom Holland as Peter Parker / Spider-Man, alongside Samuel L.
Jackson, Zendaya, Cobie Smulders, Jon Favreau, J.
Smoove, Jacob Batalon, Martin Starr, Tony Revolori,
Marisa Tomei, and Jake Gyllenhaal.
In the film, Parker is recruited by Nick Fury (Jackson) and Mysterio (Gyllenhaal)
to face the Elementals while he is on a school trip to Europe.
Discussions for a sequel to Spider-Man: Homecoming began by October
2016, and the project was confirmed later that year.
Holland, Watts, and the writers were all set to return by the end of 2017.
In 2018, Jackson and Gyllenhaal joined the cast as
Fury and Mysterio, respectively.
Holland revealed the sequel's title ahead of filming, which began that July and took place
in England, the Czech Republic, Italy, and the New York metropolitan area.
Production wrapped in October 2018.
The marketing campaign is one of the most expensive for a film ever and attempted to avoid
revealing spoilers for Avengers: Endgame prior to its April 2019 release.
Spider-Man: Far From Home premiered at the TCL Chinese Theatre in Hollywood, Los Angeles, on June 26, 2019, and was
theatrically released in the United States on July 2, as the final film in Phase Three of the MCU.
The film received positive reviews with praise for its humor, action
sequences, visuals, and the performances of Holland and Gyllenhaal.
It grossed $1.133 billion worldwide, making it the first Spider-Man film to pass the billion-dollar mark, the
fourth-highest-grossing film of 2019, and became Sony Pictures' highest-grossing film and the 24th-highest-grossing film of all time.
A sequel, Spider-Man: No Way Home, was released in December 2021.
The film explores themes of venice, italy, secret
identity, superhero, school trip, europe.
The tone is thought_provoking.